

CONTACT

Addres
Blk 6 Lot 23-B Gumamela St.

hone0938 282 4353

Email jamesgayares611@gmail.com

Greenland Cainta, Rizal, 1900.

EDUCATION

2014-2017 **BS CIVIL ENGINEERING**Polytechnic University of the Philippines

SKILLS

Math and Numbers
Microsoft Office and Microsoft CRM
Google Docs, Sheets, and Slides
Photo Editing (Canva and Phoroshop)

AutoCAD

Lead Generation Tasks

Cold Calling/Outbound Calls

Sales

Inbound Customer Service

Retention Specialist

Collections Specialist

Content Moderation

James Gayares

Virtual Assistant

PROFILE

An extremely dedicated individual with 5+ years of experience in providing stellar customer service. Solution-oriented eager to apply years of experience towards launching a successful career with an organization that will capitalize on administrative leadership while offering opportunities for ongoing professional growth in exchange for a solid work ethic, integrity, and commitment to superior performance.

EXPERIENCE

Aug 2022 - April 2023

Digital Marketing Agency I Florida, USA.

LEAD GENERATION SPECIALIST

- Email Marketing & Market Research
- Prospecting (Lead Kahuna, Generating leads)
- Handling Email Campaigns

May 2022 - Sep 2022

Restoration Growth I California, USA.

APPOINTMENT SETTER

- Outbound Calls (cold calling)
- Fulfilling VA tasks (emails , chat, sms, scheduling and monitoring)

Feb 2020 - May 2022

GoGoGrandparent I California, USA.

VIRTUAL ASSISTANT

- Lead Generation and Manage Sales Message
- Do inbound/outbound calls (Groceries and Home Services)
- Fulfilling VA tasks (filing documents, emails, and chat)

Oct 2019 - Mar 2020

Lead Pro I Laguna, Philippines

LEAD GENERATION SPECIALIST (REAL ESTATE)

- Outbound Calls (Cold Calling)
- Fulfilling VA tasks (emails , chat, sms, scheduling, and compling document)

Jul 2018 - Nov 2019

Taskus Inc. I Anonas, Quezon City. Philippines

CONTENT MODERATOR

- Filtering Advertisements for a Social Media Platform
- Tackling Trending Topics

Nov 2017 - May 2018

Alorica I Cubao, Quezon City, Philippines

CUSTOMER SERVICE REPRESENTATIVE

- Take inbound calls (Retention Specialist)
- Do outbound calls (Collection Specialist)
- Upselling

Mar 2017 - Nov 2017

Sitel PH I 1 Doña Julia Vargas Ave, Pasig, Philippines

CUSTOMER SERVICE REPRESENTATIVE

- Take inbound calls
- Upselling